there no Yes because this is our country
там не Да потому что это наша страна
Russia why do you need us what do we have
Россия зачем вы нам что нам от вашего
nothing but problems from your Donetsk and Lugansk
Донецка и Луганска одни проблемы
Problems What are you talking about you only
Проблемы Да что ты это ты только одно
know one word from Lugansk Donetsk is not a
слово знаешь от Луганска Донецка не
problem And you
проблемы А ты
dive in what is war and how people
окунись что такое война и как люди
have suffered since 1914 you  I didn't
страдали с четырнадцатого года ты не
know and it's all because of
знал а это всё из-за
you hi hi hi
вас привет привет привет
Hello Damn Can you take this side
Здравствуйте Блин А можешь эту сторону
away I'll talk to you about
отобрать я с тобой
something Well with this green cactus
поговорю чего Ну с этим кактусом зелёным
Well take it away from him It's very boring just
Ну забрать у него Скучно очень просто
against And you're nice to talk to you
противо А ты симпатично с тобой
so if that's how it goes you can  not paying
так если так-то пошло можно не обращать
attention
внимания
at all it's so
вообще это су
difficult My name is Andrey What's
сложно Меня зовут Андрей Вас как зовут
your name What's your
Как вас
name Damn what's
зовут блин
your name in principle I
вас вообще в принципе зовут Я сама
come myself what's the difference Masha
прихожу какая разница Маша
Maria not What's your name Here you are Masha I communicate with you
Мария не Как зовут Вот вы Маша с вами
Yes Masha m
Да Маша м
do you work what in what field do you work
работаете чего в какой сфере работаете
Maria She works  on
Мария Она работает на
s You know
с Знаешь
how Maria drinks Wine it's just about
такое как Мария пьёт Вино это просто про
let me take a picture of it
давай его сфоткаю
Maria what Maria You are a woman I'm telling you honestly
Мария чего Мария Вы женщина я вам честно
but I advised you If you want to
говорю но я вам советовал Если хотите с
talk to men in roulette  girlfriends
мужчинами поговорить в рулет выхо подруг
go she's a little bit like you
иди она немножко как бы
know and many men
знаете и многие мужчины
switch Tell me please
переключаются Скажите мне пожалуйста Вы
what city are you from you don't see I'm from the
из какого города ты же не видишь Я из
city where the city of Khmelnitsky
города откуда город Хмельницкий
Ukraine you have a flag behind damn how are you
Украина у тебя флаг сзади блин как ты
biting your lip Masha it's just Masha you I'm
губку прикусе Маша это просто Маша ты Я
in shock you damn  you just ooze
в шоке ты блин у от тебя прямо так веет
femininity attractiveness
женственностью притягательность
voluptuousness Listen I don't understand one thing
тельность Слушай мне вот одно непонятно
You're sitting right there in Khmelnitsky with a flag I'm
Ты в Хмельницке прямо сидишь и флагом
sitting right there and look Masha damn how you
прямо сижу и смотри Маша блин как ты
throw your hand in Oh my god why are you
ручку Закидываешь Да ёлки-палки почему
and I in different countries that are
мы с тобой в разных странах которые
fighting damn Mashenka it's just
воюют блин Машенька это просто просто
damn Where is this from  such a girl in Russia
блин Откуда такая девушка в России
just Why do you pay attention to some
просто Почему ты обращаешь на какие-то
moments How is your hand Are you a psychologist or something I am not a
моменты Как рука Ты психолог что ли Я не
psychologist Yes yes I am a psychologist I have 18
я психолог Да да я психолог у меня 18
years of practice and in 2 years I will be
лет практики и через 2 года будет
twentieth not as a psychologist But as a man
двадцатому не как психолог А как мужчина
because you are not my client  who
потому что ты не клиент мой который
came you woman quite a pretty
пришла ты женщина довольно симпатичная
woman woman and a woman who has
женщина женщина и женщина у которой
some very strong internal
очень сильно какая-то внутренняя
energy you know there are women
энергетика знаешь вот есть женщины
who are disgusting look for example oh
которые отвращает смотришь например во
yeah at her  look she understand want to
да на неё смотришь она понимаешь хочется
switch off switch from going Yes
отключиться переключиться от ийти Да
look just shut up your I look at you
смотри прож завали свою смотришь на тебя
and just want to bloom blossom
и прямо аж э хочется цвести расцветать
if you are a psychologist As you say Yes there
если ты психолог Как ты говоришь Да там
already with great experience and so on Well
уже с великим стажем и так далее Ну так
also a woman also can't be rude Yes there
же женщине тоже нельзя грубить Да там
insult and that's it  this is if it
оскорблять и всё это Это если она
works out For example Well your client and the
получается Например Ну твой клиент а
woman look we psychologists have a
женщине смотри у нас у психологов есть
code Yes if the woman is like
кодекс Да если женщина так вот как вот
this friend of yours Yes she is not that you can
эта подруга твоя Да ей не то что можно
she needs to be told that so that she
ей нужно говорить что так чтобы она
shows herself to people less and does not
меньше показывалась людям на глаза не
spoil her  comes out with this goes to
портила она ж выходит с этим идёт на
work She spoils everyone's mood in the trolleybus in the metro on the
работу Она всем в троллейбусе в метро на
street you know people
улице портит настроение понимаешь люди
wake up in the morning go a bunch of things they
проснулись утром идут куча дел они целый
have to do all day long yes a bunch of work
день должны что-то делать да куча рабо
it goes with this sour It's just brutal
оно идёт с этим кислым Это просто жесть
and you you're like Tsvetochok you're on  you
а ты ты как Цветочек ты вот на тебя
look and your soul blossoms honestly you are
смотришь и Аж душа расцветает честно ты
cool you are
крутая Ты
cool it's all clear but I just
крутая Это всё понятно но просто я
think if you are a psychologist then
считаю Если Вы психолог то
you are a spider you shouldn't at all Mitya how
паук Вы не должны вообще Мить как бы у
should you have it by you by
Вас должно быть это по Вы по выработке
years of experience
годов опыта
stasha this is back again take it away Masha
сташа это снова вернулась забери Маша
Take this one away from here You shouldn't be rude
Забери эту отсюда Вы не должны хамить
at all Masha please we are like this
вообще Маша пожалуйста мы с тобой так
damn I'm for you In short look ready Masha
блин я для тебя Короче смотри готов Маша
unbutton even this is you Lady yeah right Take
расстегнуть даже это ты Леди да ну
this one away from here I feel scared even
Забери эту отсюда мне стрёмно даже
look I'm talking to you but  I feel
смотри я с тобой разговариваю но мне
creepy that she's looking at me
стрёмно что она на меня
you didn't
смотрит ты не поняла
understand really you understand that is it's
реально понимаешь то есть это это
stupid whose mission in life is to ruin
тупо у которой миссия в жизни портить
everyone's mood with your
всем настроение своим
sour well that's how I understand it yes Well you're
кислым ну я так понимаю да А ну ты
wrong you're completely unpleasant in
ошибаешься ты неприятный совершенно во
me and in my life
мне и в моей жи понял
you got it damn Masha you  so bite your lip just
ты блин Маша ты так покуса губку просто
this is Masha Masha Masha Masha Masha and love is
это Маша Маша Маша Маша Маша а любовь
already
уже
Our
Наша
what will I sit here telling
какая будет мне тут сидеть рассказывать
you What are you thinking Mashenka you're just cool
Ты что в себя Машенька ты просто крутая
Oh Maria tell me
О Мария расскажи-ка мне
[music]
[музыка]
Maria damn And you also have Maria not that
Мария блин А у тебя тоже Мария не то что
this one has  I'm telling you what kind of European Union do you want Masha
этой Я говорю какой тебе Евросоюз Маша
Turn the camera on yourself I don't want to look at this one for
Поверни на себя камеру Я не хочу на эту
real Why look at this
смотреть реально Зачем смотреть на этою
face if with such
лицо если с такими
emotions it's just well I've never seen such a one
эмоциями это просто ну я таких ещё в
life Maria Show me your earrings you have
жизни Мария Покажи свои серёжки у тебя
Cool miniature ones
Классненький миниатюрные
Seryozha don't Switch it no
Серёже не Переключай его не
need Listen I have
надо Слушай у меня у меня
one Masha give me your question I
оди Маша давай вопросик свой я тебе
will answer you one question you haven't seen yet
отвечу на вопро один вопрос ещё не виде
Fu I have one question Well for Ukraine
Фу у меня один вопрос Ну за Украину же
right
правильно
Yes Masha relax I myself  from Kursk I'm
Да Маша расслабься Я сам из Курска я тут
trolling Ukrainians here they shout Glory to
троллю украинцев они кричат Слава
Ukraine and then I show that I'm from
Украине а я потом показываю что я из
Kursk But when I find sex Yes I'm
Курска Но когда я нахожу сексуаль Да я
from Kursk Yes but when I find women I
из Курска Да но когда я нахожу женщин я
don't talk to them about politics
не о политике с ними
from Kursk from the
говорю с кур с
European Union initially wait he said
Евросоюз изначально подожди он сказал
where mills from  and why is it that I
откуда мельниц а почему так это я
said it from the mills Look, I imagine
говорил с мельниц Смотри я представляю
that I am from Ukraine, I made the flag of the European Union,
что я из Украины я сделал флаг Евросоюза
this is not a flag, this is a green background
это не флаг это Зелёный фон там
when Ukrainians say
подставляется когда украинцы говорят
Glory to Ukraine, I show them that I am from
Слава Украине Я им показываю что я из
Kursk, I show Russia, you understand,
Курской показываю Россия понимаешь
show Listen, well, we ourselves are from Donetsk, in
показва Слушай ну мы сами с Донецка
general  in fact A we live in Russia
вообще на самом деле А живём в России
Donetsk How long ago did you move my
Донец Как давно переехала
husband and I arrived in the fifteenth year in the
мы с мужем приехали в пятнадцатом году в
Nizhny Novgorod region who will tell
Нижегородскую область кому расска
Wait Stop Stop Stop Stop Why did you
Подожди Стоп стоп стоп стоп а что вы
leave
уехали Прикинь в четырнадцатом году
Just imagine the war started in 1914 So wait we
началась война Так подожди мы сейчас
attacked Kursk because of your Donetsk And you went to Nizhny
напали А вы в Нижний
Novgorod, listen, wait, let's
Новгород слышь подожди давай тут
figure this out I mean Kursk was
разберёмся В смысле изза нас на Курск
attacked because of us Well, it all started from its own  because of you
напали Ну из сво началось из-за вас
Donetsk yes Putin went to defend Donetsk
донецких да Путин пошёл защитим Донецк
Yes here Let's figure it out now if you are
Да тут Давай теперь разберёмся если ты
so smart and so wonderful How did the
такой умный и такой прекрасный С чего
war start in the fourteenth year Well,
началась война в четырнадцатом году А ну
tell me please is it you and Kiev
расскажи мне пожалуйста это вы с Киевом
media Figure out why your war
СМИ Разберитесь с чего у вас война
started no Mashenka will already be there  now
началась нет Машенька уже будет сейчас
tell me why the war started in m
расскажи мне почему началась война в м
year you know you didn't share something with the Maidan
году знат вы что-то там с майданом не
there you Yanukovych your Yanukovych to
поделили там вы Янукович ваш Янукович к
us in Russia Why Wait And now
нам в Россию Зачем Подожди А теперь
tell me why the war started in m
расскажи мне почему в м войну война
Why was it I lived in Kursk
началась Почему было я се в Курске жил
I live on your  Donetsk
мне на ваш Донецк
was because it wasn't Donetsk people who were jumping
было потому что не Донецкие люди скакали
on
на
Maidan you to us Why should we Kursk guys
Майдане вы нам Почему мы курские ребята
now die for your
должны сейчас умирать за ваш
Donetsk what
Донец какой
you do not defend your Donetsk with your husband in
ты не защищаю свой Донецк твоим мужем в
Nizhny Novgorod And I have a Classmate
Нижний Новгород А у меня Одноклассник
Sanya Prokhorov Kursk region last
Саня Прохоров Курской области в прошлом
month Listen I want you all to
месяце Послушай я хочу чтоб вы все
fight And I came to Russia and I am waiting for
воевали А я приехала в Россию и жду чтоб
you have conquered everything and everything Just imagine Listen,
вы все завоевали и все Прикинь Слышишь
we in the Kursk region must fight for
мы в Курской области должны воевать за
your
твой
Donetsk
Донецк
Listen, the Volo wanted it that way and Donetsk is
Послушай воло так захотелось и Донец это
Bue is It is convenient for him that everyone
Буе это Ему удобно чтобы везде все
fights everywhere and Donetsk is simply a
воевали а Донецк просто-напросто это
buffer zone if he wanted it,
буферная зона если бы он бы захотел бы
he would have thrown it back a long time ago  from the front line of
он уже давно бы отбросил от линии фронта
all these and this is not
всех этих а этого не
wanted when Crimea you understand when we
хочется когда Крым понимаешь мы когда
took Crimea for ourselves there at least you can go
Крым себе забрали там хоть можно поехать
here I went from the Kursk region in STM in
вот я я с Курской области ездил в СТМ
the year to Crimea to rest and your Donetsk is needed
году в Крым отдыхать а ваш Донецк нужен
Motorola Givi In short we need you in our
Моторолы Гиви Короче вы нам нуж в свою
Ukraine with this Kiev  be friends we
Украину с этим Киевом дружите вы нам
need you Study
нужны Изучи
Study why the war started I was born
Изучи изза чего началась война Я родился
in Russia I am a citizen of the Russian
в России я гражданин Российской
Federation and  you showed up yes you you you
Федерации а ты припёрлась да вам вам вы
came you benefits Let's give everything to you
приехали вам пособие Давайте всё вам
Let's
Давайте
go I know because my mother's
Пошли я знаю потому что м у моей мамы
pension is small and everyone in Donetsk gets paid
пенсия маленькая м всем донецким платят
you get paid for what you
вам платят за то что вы
eat you don't get
вые тебе не платят
benefits How much benefits do they give you did your
пособи Сколько вам пособие дают у тебя
house burn down or something  you And what about you Your
дом сгорел или что у тебя А что вы Ваш
house yours what should I pay for your house
дом ваши что я должен платить за ваш дом
in
в
Donetsk go go to Donetsk protect it you
Донецке едь едь в Донецке защищай его ты
to Nizhny Novgorod you are sitting in Nizhny
в Нижний Новгород ты сидишь в Нижнем
Novgorod 700 km from Donetsk And we in
Новгороде 700 км от Донецка А мы в
Kursk should die
Курске должны погибать
got it Do you hear you come to us in the Kursk
понял Слышишь ты ты приедь нам в курскую
region  and tell this come and tell the people in
область и скажи этот приедь и людям в
Kursk region because of you because of
Курской области скажи изза вас из-за
your everything legal that your
вашего всего законного то что ваш
president wanted this we suffered for what
президент захотел это мы страдали чего
years you knew how we lived And you
года ты знал как мы жили А тебе
were me Yes because this is our country
была мне Да потому что это наша страна
Russia why do you need us what do we need from  your
Россия зачем вы нам что нам от вашего
Donetsk and Lugansk have nothing but problems
Донецка и Луганска одни проблемы
Problems What are you talking about you only
Проблемы Да что ты это ты только одно
know one word from Lugansk Donetsk is not a
слово знаешь от Луганска Донецка не
problem And you
проблемы А ты
take a dip what is this  war and how people
окунись что такое война и как люди
suffered since the fourteenth year you didn't
страдали с четырнадцатого года ты не
know and it's all because of you These are your
знал а это всё из-за вас Это ваши
problems and what do we have to do with Russia it was you who
проблемы причём мы Россия это вы
started talking porridge with Kiev and you
заговорили кашу с Киевом вы и
figure out what you are suffering in the Kurtka region
разбираетесь что вы в курткой области
These are your problems and not ours
страдаете Это ваши проблемы а не наши
listen you couldn't agree  we
слуша вы не могли Договориться с Киевом
should have already decided with Kiev there the language is Russian
надо было уже решать там язык русский
Ukrainian we What does it have to do with you getting
украинский мы Причём тут что вы полезли
into our Russia Putin Take us to Russia
к нам в Россию Путин Забери нас в Россию
yes I should have personally talked to
да я должна была лично разговаривать с
Kiev because of you Look because of you
Киевом из-за вас Смотри из-за вас на нас
sanctions were imposed on us because of you  sanctions because of
санкции наложили из-за вас санкции из-за
you We have a dollar business Why do
вас У нас доллар бизнес пошёл Почему у
our parents have a small pension because of
наших родителей пенсия маленькая из-за
your sanctions because damn you
ваших санкций из-за того что блин вы
came you live on our money in this
приехали вы живёте на наши деньги в этой
Novgorod region yes You live in
Новгородской области да Вы живёте в
our apartments I live on your money and
наших квартирах Я на твои деньги живу а
Well tell me please I rent
Ну расскажи мне пожалуйста Я снимаю
an apartment you I rent a tira and rata my
квартиру ты Я снимаю тиру и рата у меня
husband works at a factory I work that's why
муж работает на заводе Я работаю вот из
our men have no work
этого нашим мужикам нету работы потому
because yours came and and  I'll take it for
что ваши по приезжали да и забираю за
a trifle, you don't want to do it, listen,
мелочь пожи делать не хотите слышишь
lazybones, we're on our own land,
лентяй мы на своей земле жим
Russian press And I'm also Russian, imagine No
русской А я тоже русская прикинь Не
Yes, and you, what, did you separate from us in the year
Да вы а вы что в дем году отделились от
Yes, your Kravchuk Yes, you, yes, ran there,
нас Да ваш Кравчук Да вы да бегали там
Donbass Yes, why on the right Yes, what are you then,
Донбасс Да справа почему Да что вы тогда
you  voted in the referendum
вы же проголосовали на референдуме за то
for an independent Ukraine Yes and then
что была незалежная Украина Да а потом
yes then Putin see troops help VOM
да потом Путин види войска помоги ВОМ
understood how many years
поняли те сколько лет
Gorbachev
Горбачёв
Note urine
Прим моча
[music]
[музыка]
Where were you before the 2nd year deno pergo
Где вы были до 2го года дено перго
why were you
почему
silent where were you how were they they will say
молчали где были как были они те скажут
that
что
Gorbachev And for  Yushchenko who are you for these
Горбач А за Ющенко кто вы за эти
oranges you voted in Donetsk too
помаранчева вы голосовали в Донецке тоже
we are
мы
the task of Yakovich you in 200 ko
зада яковича вы в 200 ко
Donetsk having presented who betrayed Yushchenko
донецки предъяв кто предал Ющенко
Yanukovych and Yanukovych is
Януковича а Янукович
clearly stirring up emotions but nothing like
оче эмоции разводит по а ниче же яко
golden toilets and betrayed
золотыми унитазами и предал
Donetsk In short it is you Why did
Донецк В смысле короче это вы Почему вы
n't you come out for him  Why didn't they provide
не вышли за него Почему не обеспечили
him
ему
with security?  hear like
безопасность слышишь лайк
squeak comment letter to my Telegram right
писка комент пись на мий Telegram прямо
now axis VN
зараз ось ВН
apok this is very and very important YouTube is busy
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
with us through scarg or in ny ban and very
нас через скарг ор в ньй бан и дуже
many videos I do not show people at times I do not
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams so that
показуе информация про стримы тому для
my Mali operational links are
того щоб ми Мали оперативный звязок
written directly  now and while there in telegram
пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в телегра
okrim video there is also interesting and useful
окрим вдео ще теж цикава и корисна
information and we are obliged to you to keep
информация и ми повинни з вами тримати
constant operational links
постийний оперативный звязок
independently in that will show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Slava ukraini
YouTube Слава украини
subscribe and
подпишись а